Right.
We're rocking it here.
As the thing says, education quotes that rock my world.
So by now you're at the end of our section and hopefully you've figured out some of the basics.
So what we want to do in this concluding thing is show you something really cool and give you a challenge.
Joshua are they up to it?
Yeah.
You reckon they are?
Yeah, they can do it.
Ah, okay.
He's got confidence in you.
I'm not too sure.
So let's see what you can do.
So firstly we just want to show you something really cool.
As you already know, your site is this HTML code basically is interpreted by Chrome or your browser
and it shows you the page.
Now what you can do is you can go and view the source code to any page.
It doesn't matter which one, but we'll use this one simply by right clicking and down the bottom.
Here in Chrome you will see view Page source.
Now if you're using another browser, invariably it's going to be in one of the options where you can
view.
For example, you can get to the same things under view developer here.
So depending on what browser you're using there'll be somewhere where you can view the page source.
So I'm right clicking and I can click view the page source.
And here we go.
We're going to see what exists inside that code.
There we go.
So that's our code.
That's exactly what we wrote.
It looks exactly the same as we had before.
That's the actual code.
We were developing it in sublime and here it is.
So it's basically taking this code and interpreting it as that web page.
So all of our codes, our links, everything here now that used to look like craziness to you before
it now makes it makes sense.
It makes sense baby.
So what else we got here Josh okay so another option with Chrome you have this inspect.
So that basically brings you to this where you see if we go here that's the body.
Party.
He has a party margin and all of that kind of stuff.
Um, other than that, you can select like a specific thing.
So let's say if we selected this and you can inspect that and say what, what, what what that was made
up of.
Yeah.
So now you see over here.
Okay.
This is made on a tag.
And an interesting thing is you can actually change this.
So if we go to tag you.
Um, there we go.
If we change it like that now, you'll see.
I changed it from bold to underline.
Okay.
So it's obviously just changing it in terms of a display, but it's showing you so you can immediately
jump to a piece or something and say well where is the HTML code for this particular piece.
What's it look like?
And even change it.
Yeah.
So now you can see obviously this is not going to affect the website, um, to anyone else.
So yeah, it's just merely a way in which you can actually look at what's going on.
Yeah.
If you refresh this is going to be gone.
So you could then make that change to your original source code again.
Yeah.
So that's just a very interesting thing that you can know about a little, uh, cool thing you can do
with Chrome.
All right.
So there we have it.
That's very cool.
That's our site.
And if you want to close that, you're going to go back to how it was originally.
Nothing has changed.
So you've learned some cool and rocking things.
Do you guys reckon you're up to it?
I reckon you're up to putting some code like this together.
Okay, right.
So here is the thing.
If you haven't already done so, your assignment is to create a rocking site like you've got here with
a couple of images below that using a table, some text, making use of a combination of H1, H2 and
whatever headers you like, and some of the formatting and something that looks formatted like this.
It's very important that you do this, because you're going to be bringing this all together in our
next section, where we're going to try and build something which is a multi-page site, and we want
you to be sure that you know how to do this.
So put it together.
And as an added little challenge, see if you can figure out how you can adjust the widths of these
columns.
Remember this is a table.
This is a row.
And we've got our table data sitting in each of the rows as we have here our various table data.
Is there a way you could use with anyone any clues that we can spread out these.
So you got to find a tag or it's not a tag, it's an actually an addition to the TD tag that can.
Well that works with the TD tag and our TR tags that can adjust the width.
It's not going to be too hard to figure out what the width and the column width and all of those.
You can figure it out, so see if you can figure it out.
Set up something similar to this and see if you can even fiddle with the width a little bit.
Right.
So that's your challenge I reckon you're up to it.
And that's what we want to leave you with.
And from here on out, we're going to pick up the pace and do something super exciting in the next section
as we pull it all together.